// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the output of print(2 ** 3)?",
        answer: "8",
        options: [
            "6",
            "8",
            "9",
            "5"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which operator is used for floor division?",
        answer: "//",
        options: [
            "///",
            "/",
            "%",
            "//"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What keyword is used to create a loop in Python?",
        answer: "for",
        options: [
            "foreach",
            "loop",
            "for",
            "while"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What do we use to define a block of code in Python?",
        answer: "Indentation",
        options: [
            "Key",
            "Brackets",
            "Indentation",
            "Parentheses"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What data type is the object below? L = [1, 23, 'hello', 1]",
        answer: "List",
        options: [
            "List",
            "Dictionary",
            "Tuple",
            "Set"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following function converts a string to a float in python?",
        answer: "float()",
        options: [
            "int()",
            "long()",
            "float()",
            "str()"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the output of 'Hello'[-1]?",
        answer: "'o'",
        options: [
            "'H'",
            "'e'",
            "'o'",
            "Error"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which operator is used in Python to import modules?",
        answer: "import",
        options: [
            "#",
            "import",
            "using",
            "include"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the output of print(type(10))?",
        answer: "<class 'int'>",
        options: [
            "<class 'int'>",
            "<type 'int'>",
            "<class 'number'>",
            "int"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following is not a core data type in Python?",
        answer: "Class",
        options: [
            "Lists",
            "Dictionary",
            "Tuples",
            "Class"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which of the following will run without errors?",
        answer: "round(45.8)",
        options: [
            "round(6352.898,2,5)",
            "round()",
            "round(7463.123,2,1)",
            "round(45.8)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What is the correct syntax to output the type of a variable or object in Python?",
        answer: "print(type(x))",
        options: [
            "print(typeof x)",
            "print(type(x))",
            "print(typeOf(x))",
            "print(type of x)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "What is the correct way to create a tuple?",
        answer: "x = (1, 2, 3)",
        options: [
            "x = tuple(1, 2, 3)",
            "x = [1, 2, 3]",
            "x = {1, 2, 3}",
            "x = (1, 2, 3)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which of the following is not a valid Python tuple?",
        answer: "x = (0,)",
        options: [
            "x = (0, 1, 2, 3)",
            "x = ()",
            "x = (0,)",
            "All of the above are valid"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "What is the output of print(0.1 + 0.2 == 0.3)?",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False",
            "0.3",
            "Error"
        ]
    }

];